softness can overcome hardness, but hardness can overcome softness
juuyokugou wo seishimashite gouyokujuu motatsu
if you're too focused on showing off, my alarm will go off
muchuu de kakkou tsukete mo hijou beru ga naru
walk fifty steps forward in a reckless style
gojuuppo ijou mo saki aruite chottotsumoushinna sutairu
you're moody and do as you please; no matter what I do, you ignore me
jiyuu de kibunya no kimi wa douyattatte mushi
there's a mystery that no one can solve, I shiver when the wind blows
darenimo tokenai nazo ga aru fukidashita kaze ni furueteru
I'll unravel this maze
kono meiro wo hodoite yaru
you laughed, will it rain tomorrow?
kimi ga waratta ashita wa ame kai
the wise light flickers
soumeina hikari ga chikachika hikaru
you've got to focus your eyes before the future changes
me wo korasanakucha mirai ga kawatte shimau mae ni
I'm sure, I'm sure this moment will be swept away
kitto kitto ima wo saratte iku
I have to be with you, otherwise the future might dry up
kimi to janakucha mirai wa kawaite shimau no kamo
hurry up, because I'm sure that we'll smile back on this moment
isoge kitto ima wo waratte iku
（マダラ）ここは　かつて
修練の洞窟と呼ばれた場所。
This place used to be called
the "Training Cave" long ago.
（ゼツ）ねぇ　その新しい術
限定月読って→
Hey, so what kind of new jutsu
is the Limited Tsukuyomi?
どんな術なんだい？
（マダラ）無限月読の試作だ。
It's a prototype of
the Infinite Tsukuyomi.
まずは術にはめる
対象者の望むものを→
First, you need to check out
the desires of your target.
調べる必要がある。
フッ…。
（ナルト）せっかくの休暇も
今日で終わりか。
Since this is the last day
of my R & R,
ってことで
明日からの活力を養うため→
I need to re-energize
for tomorrow.
大事にとっておいた
個数限定プレミアムラーメンを→
So I'm going to bust out
my reserve
思い切って　開けちゃうってばよ。
of that limited edition premium
ramen that I've been saving.
って　つまんねえな…。
This is boring...
よし。
All right...
ジャ～ン！　これ　な～んだ？
Tadah! Guess what this is?
すっげえ！
限定プレミアムラーメンじゃん！
Wow! It's the limited edition
premium ramen!
どこの店行っても売り切れで
手に入らねえやつ。
Every store is sold out of it.
You can't buy it anywhere!
この個数限定プレミアムラーメンを
食いたいか？
Want some limited edition
premium ramen?!
（２人）お～！
本当に食いてえか？
– Yeah!
Do you really want some?!
（２人）お～！
本当に食いてえか？
– Yeah!
Do you really, really want some?!
（２人）お～！　食いてえぞ！
– Yeah! We want some!
じゃあ　ラーメン争奪
ウルトラトランプ大会を→
Well then...
Let's have an ultra-super card game
with this ramen as the prize!
開催するってばよ！
（２人）イェ～イ！
– Yay!
FIRE
（テンテン）あ～　疲れた。
I'm so tired.
でも　長かった任務も終わったし
明日から休暇だ。
But my long mission is over and
I get a break from tomorrow!
（ガイ）おぉ　カカシ！
任務引き継ぎを　よろしく頼んだ。
Oh, Kakashi! Please take over for me!
（カカシ）は～いはい　了解。
Sure, sure. Roger that.
（テンテン）早速リフレッシュよ！
銭湯でも行こう。
I need to refresh myself.
Let's go to the bathhouse.
（ネジ）うん。　リー　お前も行くか？
Yeah.
Lee, are you going
to come with us?
（リー）僕は結構です。
No thanks. I would like
to train from now.
これから
修業したいと思っているんで。
えらいね。
でも　あんま無理すると→
That's so admirable of you.
But don't overdo it or your body
won't be able to keep up—
体がついていかなくなる…。
リー！　お前ってやつは…。
Lee! That's my boy!
青春しまくりだ！
クソ～　コンチクショウ！
You're brimming with youth!
Damn! Damn it!
俺も　その修業につきあう！
いくぞ　リー！
I will train with you!
Let's go, Lee!
（リー）ファイ！
《大丈夫？》
Fight!
Will he be okay?
ついてこい！　青春フルパワーだ！
Follow me!
Onward, with the full power
of youth!
そりゃ！　あっ！？　うわ～っと…。
SUPERHUMAN STRENGTH
STRONG FOUNDATION
《ダメだよね　やっぱ…》
Nope, I figured as much.
あぁ～　ガイ先生！
立って！　立ってください！
Guy Sensei!
Stand... Please stand
and face tomorrow!
明日に向かって！
リー君。
Lee... His body won't do what
he tells it to anymore.
この人は　体がすでに
ついていってないのだよ。
死なないで…　ガイ先生！
Please don't die... Guy Sensei!
あぁ～　僕を…　僕を
立派な忍にしてくれるって…。
You told me you would see to it...
リー君　こっちは引き受けるから
代わりに　サクラとナルトの伝言を→
– Lee, I'll take over here.
– that I would become a fine shinobi!
– So can you take a message...
– You promised! Guy Sensei!
お願いできるかな！？
え？
to Sakura and Naruto?
Huh?
（メブキ）あんたは　どうして
そう　だらしないの！
Why are you so untidy?
洗濯物は端を合わせて
ちゃんと　たたみなさい！
Match up the seams
when you fold laundry!
（サクラ）文句言うなら　自分でやって。
Do it yourself if
you're going to complain!
なんで　わざわざ休日に
お説教されなきゃいけないのよ。
I don't need lectures
on my day off!
休日じゃないと
あんた　いないでしょ。
The only time you're home
is on your day off!
（サクラ）当たり前でしょ。
（メブキ）当たり前なら口答えするな！
Duh! Isn't that obvious?!
If it's obvious, don't talk back!
（キザシ）サクラ！
お母さんの言うとおりだぞ。
Sakura... Mom's right.
親子ゲンカなんか　いいかげんに塩！
So stop arguing and
don't be so... salty!
なんつって…。
Right?
TABLE SALT
え？
リーさん　どうしたの？
Huh?
Lee! What's up?
あ　いえ　お取り込み中　すみません
任務のことで…。
Oh, I'm sorry to interrupt.
It's about your mission...
あぁ　任務の打ち合わせね。
今　行きます。
Oh, the prep meeting for
our next mission?
I'll be right there!
すみません　任務は
明日　朝６時　集合との→
Sorry to bother you,
I have a message for you
"to assemble tomorrow at 6 a.m."
伝言を預かりまして。
いいんです
抜け出す口実ができたから。
It's okay. You gave me
an excuse to leave.
今日くらい
のんびり過ごしたいしね。
I want to take it easy today,
you know?
ありがとう。
So thanks!
さて　次はと…。
Next up is...
やった～！
チクショウ！　ツイてねえ！
Yes!
Damn, I'm not having any luck!
危ねえ　いきなり脱落する
ところだったぜ。
Whoa, that was a close call.
おい　お前　イカサマしてんじゃ
ねえだろうな？
Hey, you!
You'd better not be cheating!
イエ～イ！　弱いやつほど
よく吠える。
It's always the weak
who complain.
なんだと！？
やめろってばよ。
What did you say?!
Cut it out, ya know.
You're all me.
俺ら　みんな
俺なんだからよ。
お前　どっちの味方なんだよ？
Whose side are you
on anyway?!
どっちと言われても…。
Well, now that you ask...
やり直しを要求する！
I demand that we start over!
負け犬の遠吠え。
許せねえ！
The loser sure can whine!
I've had it! Let's go outside!
外出やがれ！
ったく…。
Sheesh...
って　俺　勝ったのか　負けたのか
よくわかんねえ！
I don't know if I won or lost...
はぁ…。
休日の最後の日に
俺は　何をやっているんだ。
What am I doing by myself
on my last day off?
やっぱ　一人はむなしいってばよ。
It's lonely, after all.
《ナルト君…》
≪（チョウジ）ねぇ　行こうよ　焼き肉。
Naruto...
Hey, let's go eat some barbeque.
（チョウジ）焼肉Ｑなら　１テーブル
１，５００両で食べ放題だし→
It's 1500 ryo for a table at Barbe-Q
and it's all you can eat.
３人で割り勘しても…
えっと　いくらだっけ？
If we split it, it's...
How much is that per person?
（シカマル）５００両だよ。　とにかく→
500 ryo.
任務終わったばっかだし
俺は　飯よか風呂だな。
Well, we just finished our mission.
I prefer a bath to food right now.
（サクラ）私も　お風呂に１票。
（キバ）赤丸　毛が土で→
My vote's for a bath too.
Akamaru, you're covered in dirt.
ドロドロになっちまったな。
これじゃ　茶丸になっちまうぜ。
I should change your name
to Chamaru as in "brown."
（赤丸）クゥ～ン。
（シノ）その道理はおかしい。
なぜなら→
Your logic is off.
本来　白い毛なのに
赤丸だからだ。
It's because Akamaru
has white fur,
but his name means "red."
だとしたら　今の赤丸は　白丸で
なければならないのであって。
So Akamaru should be called
Shiromaru as in "white."
（キバ）お前　何言ってんか
わかんねえ！
I don't have a clue about
what you're saying.
そういうこと言ってんじゃねえ！
All I was saying to Akamaru is
that I need to clean him up!
赤丸を　きれいにしねえとな
ってこと！
（ヒナタ）だったら
銭湯に行ったらいいと思う。
Then you should take him
to the bathhouse too.
それはダメだ。　なぜなら→
That's impossible.
犬は　銭湯に入れないからだ。
It's because dogs aren't allowed
in a bathhouse.
（キバ）そんなの　どうにかすりゃ
いいだろ！
Well then, I just have to figure
something out, right?!
((早速　リフレッシュよ。
銭湯でも行こう))
I need to refresh myself!
Let's go to the bathhouse!
うおっ！
はい　ナルト君！
– Yikes!
– Hi, Naruto!
みんなを誘って
銭湯へ　レッツゴーです！
Let's round up everyone and
go to the bathhouse!
皆さん！　ここは一緒に仲間同士→
Everyone! Let's all go together
to the bathhouse!
銭湯へ行きましょう！
（キバ）なんで　言い出しっぺのリーが
来てねえんだよ。
Lee's the one who suggested this,
so how come he's not here?
あぁ　修業の逆立ち歩きが
３，０００歩残ってんだってよ。
Yeah, well... He still has 3000
hand-stand steps left to go in training.
でも　終わったら　すぐ来るって。
He said he'll come
as soon as he's done.
ご苦労なこって。
Gotta hand it to him.
《ゲジマユのやつ　俺が一人だからって
気を遣いやがって》
Bushy Brow was being thoughtful
because I was all by myself...
ゲジマユも　早く来ねえかな。
I sure hope he gets here soon!
《一人で　ゆっくりしようと
思ってたのに→
Just when I thought I'd relax alone...
なんで　みんながいるのよ。
Why's everyone here too?
まぁ　いいけどね》
Oh well, whatever.
はぁ　任務後のお湯は
五臓六腑にしみるねぇ。
After a mission, a nice, hot soak
soothes all the way to your vital organs!
（いの）テンテンさん　なんか
おっさんくさいわよ。
Tenten, you sound like an old man.
フフフ。
ヒナタ？　別に恥ずかしがって
隠そうとしなくてもいいじゃない。
Hinata... Don't be embarrassed
and try to hide them.
女同士なんだし。
You're among women here.
もっとゆっくり
お湯に浸かれば？
Relax and let yourself go
in the bath.
う　うん…。
U-Uh-huh...
その…　なんか　浮いてきちゃって。
Well... It's just that
they keep floating up...
《サクラ：ヒナタが　いつも
うらやましいと思うわ。
I'm jealous of Hinata.
Of her chest that is...
その膨らみだけは》
急がねば。　１，８５２　１，８５３　１，８５４。
I must hurry.
1852... 1853... 1854...
ゲジマユのやつ　まだやってんのかな？
I wonder if Bushy Brow is still at it?
たく　クソまじめっつうか
空気読めねえっつうか。
That guy is so diligent...
and so hard to figure out...
いつものことだ。　なぜなら
やつは修業の虫だからだ。
This is nothing new.
The reason is he's got
the training bug.
だが　俺はそういう虫が
気に入っている。
I like bugs like that.
もっと大きな心で
仲間を見るべきだ。
You must see your comrades in
a more generous light.
《前の任務で
１人仲間外れにしたこと→
This guy is still smarting
from the time
今でも根に持ってんだな　こいつ》
he was left out of a mission.
さすがいいこと言うってばよ。
大きな心…　ん？
Wow! What a great thing to say!
A big heart...
うわぁ！　シノの…　シノの下半身
あたりにでっかい幼虫おる！
Shino... Shino, there's a giant larva
near your groin!
蟲使いなら体に虫を飼ってて
当たり前だろ。
He's an insect user. It's obvious
he'd have 'em on his body.
シノ　お前　男として　いろんな意味で
まぶしいやつだってばよ。
Shino... You're one guy I admire
in more ways than one!
そうか。
おい　聞いたか　キバ。
Oh yeah?
Hey, did you hear that, Kiba?
ワンワン。
ん？
Huh?
そいつは赤丸だよ。
犬のままじゃ入れねえから→
Huh?
That's Akamaru.
They don't allow dogs in here,
獣人変化して連れ込んだ。
so I used Man-Beast Transformation
so he could come.
うわっ！
うわっ　わ～！
ク～ン。
Strike!
（チョウジ）ストライク！　なんつって。
Not!
気ぃつけろ　チョウジ。
（シカマル）湯が減っちまったな。
Watch it, Choji!
The water level went down.
たく　どうする気だ？
Now what're we gonna do?
– How're we supposed to take a soak now?
– Sorry!
騒いでるわね。
– They're making a lot of noise.
– Sory won't cut it!
それにしても
よく出てこれたわね。
I'm surprised you were able to join us.
あんたのお母さんうるさいのに。
ほんと　うざい。
Your mother's pretty strict.
Yeah, she's such a pain!
My mom piles on the chores
when I'm off too.
うちも休日は　こき使われるよ。
And If I complain,
断ろうもんなら
お父さん心乱身で。
my dad threatens to use
the Mind Destruction Jutsu on me!
ちょっとうらやましいな。
はぁ？
I'm a bit jealous though...
Huh?
Choji! Use your Expansion Jutsu.
チョウジ　倍化の術やってくれ。
え？　なんで？
Huh? Why?
いいから。
わかったよ。
Just do it.
Okay.
倍化の術。
Expansion Jutsu!
Hey, the water level went up.
お～　湯が増えた。　なんでだ？
Why?
増えたはいいが
かなり暑苦しいな。
There's more water,
but it's awfully tight in here.
ハハッ。
It's fun being with them, after all.
《やっぱこいつらといると
楽しいや。
Much better than being alone.
一人でいるより　ずっと。
あいつ　今頃どうしてっかな？
I wonder what he's doing now.
あいつだけは変わっちまった。
He's the only one who's changed.
あいつだって変わらなきゃ
この場所に…》
If he didn't change,
he'd be here too.
サスケ…　なんで？
Sasuke? How come you're...?
どうかしたか？
Something wrong?
What's with that look, Naruto?
You planning something?
なんだ　ナルト。
その何かたくらむような顔は。
俺は物思いにふけってた
だけだってばよ。
I was just lost in thought!
何かよからぬことを考えていた
のではあるまいな。
You'd better not be up to your tricks!
なっ　なに？
ノゾキだ！
え！？
W-What?
As in Peeping Tom!
Huh?
（いの）もっかい　もっかい…。
– Stop!
– Do that again!
I get it. On the other side is...
そうか　この向こうは…。
《そういう楽しみが
あったってばよ》
There's also that sort of fun!
あぁ　なんとも言えねえ
いい湯だったってばよ。
That bath felt so good...
おい　お前　湯に浸かったか？
Hey, did you even soak?
２，９９８。
2998...
Just a few more...
あと少し。
ナルト君　待っていてください。
Naruto! Please wait for me!
２，９９９。
Two thousand... nine hundred...
ninety-nine.
あっ…。
ノゾキポイントは　えっと…。
Now, to get a nice peek at...
何だ　何だ！？
クゥ～ン。
What was that?!
That Naruto!
ナルトめ！
イタタ…。
Owwww...
リー！
なんで　リーさんが！？
– Lee!
– What are you doing here, Lee?
てめえ　ロック・リー！
Rock Lee, you...!
もしかして
ノゾキしてやがったのか？
You were peeping?!
ち　違います！
N-No!
これは　修業中
何かに引っかかって→
I got stuck on something
during training and...
偶然の事故です。
It was really an accident!
へぇ
わざわざ　風呂屋の屋根で？
Oh, really?
Training on the bathhouse roof?
おかしいだろ。　ぶっ殺す！
Like we believe you...
I'm gonna pummel you!
ち…　ちが…。
N-N-No...
ゲジマユ。
Bushy Brow...
（ネジ）ナルト！　やっぱり　お前か！
Naruto!
It was you, after all!
違うって。
（いの）しらばっくれるな　ロック・リー！
N-Not.
Don't act innocent, Rock Lee!
ロック・リー？
Rock Lee?
何があった！？
キャッ！
What happened?
ナ…　ナルト君。
Naruto...
聞いてよ。
リーが　ノゾキをしていたの！
Listen to us!
Lee was sneaking a peek!
なんだと！？　けしからん。
What? How disgusting!
オラ　オラ　オラ！　しらばっくれんな！
See, see! So don't pretend!
ゲジマユ　お前…。
Bushy Brow, you...
（いの）おわっ！
（テンテン）逃げた！
He's running away!
（いの）
野郎　逃げるとは余計　怪しい！
Running away makes him
even more suspicious!
（テンテン）みんな　追うわよ！
（チョウジ）痛いなぁ。
Let's go after him!
– That hurt!
– What a terrible guy!
（いの）待て～！
（ネジ）とんでもないやつだ。
((みなさん！　ここは一緒に
仲間同士　銭湯へ行きましょう。
Let's round up everyone
and go to the bathhouse!
ナルト君　みんなを誘って
銭湯へレッツらゴーです！
Naruto! Let's all go together!
せっかくの休日です。
It's our day off!
一人じゃなくて
みんなで楽しみましょう！
Don't stay by yourself.
Let's have fun with everyone!
ただ　僕はまだ
修業ノルマが残っています。
But I still have some training
to finish up.
(自分にウソはつけません。
終わり次第すぐに駆けつけます))
I never lie to myself... I'll rush over
as soon as I'm done!
《俺のために→
Bushy Brow rounded up everyone,
just for my sake.
みんなに
声をかけてくれたゲジマユが…》
そんなこと　するはずねえ！
He wouldn't do such a thing!
（ネジ）見損なったぞ　リー。
I misjudged you, Lee!
違うんです！　屋根づたいに
ジャンプする修業をしていて。
You're wrong!
I was training, jumping from
roof to roof and...
ほら　破れてるでしょ？
See, it's torn.
何かに引っかかってバランスを崩して
偶然　女子の脱衣所に。
I got stuck on something
and lost my balance...
and accidentally fell into
the women's changing room.
問答無用！
あっ…。
Forget the excuses!
みんな　落ち着いて！
本当に偶然かもしれないじゃない。
Calm down, everyone.
It really could have been an accident!
サクラさん…。
うっさい！　疑わしきは　ボコる！
S-Sakura...
Shut up! I'm going to beat
the truth out of him!
ちょっと待て！
あ！？
Hey, hold it!
ゲジマユは　そんなやつじゃねえ。
ナルト君。
Bushy Brow's not like that!
Naruto...
ゲジマユは俺らの仲間だぞ。
Bushy Brow's our friend!
やってねえっつってんなら
やってねえ。
If he says he's innocent,
he's innocent!
証拠もねえのに仲間を疑うなんて
やめろってばよ！
Don't judge him when
you don't even have the proof!
仲間を信じろ！
Trust your comrade!
確かに　そうかもね。
You could be right.
私も　ついカッとしちゃって。
I just lost it and...
ナ…　ナルト君…。
N-Naruto...
もっと大きい心を胸に。
Have a big heart...
Oh...!
あ…。
（みんな）あっ！
– Huh?!
最も小さい下着を胸に。
どう見ても　あの下着は…。
A very small piece of underwear
that could only be...
私の。
Mine.
ナ…　ナルト君。
N-Naruto...
ぐぉ～　ぬぉ～！
Damn you...
どうした？
（サクラ）下着泥棒が！
What's up?
You underwear thief!
な…　何！？
とぼけるんじゃない　うずまきナルト。
What?
Don't you dare act innocent,
Naruto Uzumaki!
あ～っ！
俺がしたのは
ノゾキだけだっつうの！
I just peeked, is all.
しかも未遂だし。
今日は最悪の日だってばよ。
Not only that, my attempt failed.
This is the worst day of my life.
いって～。
なんで俺が　こんな目に…。
Owww... Why did I have to
go through this?!
やっぱり　一人が虚しいからって→
I knew it!
I shouldn't have tagged along
even though I was lonely!
ついていったのが
間違いだったんだってばよ。
もう　あいつらの…。
Forget those guys... Huh?
なんでか　リーが遊びに行こう
ってんで来ちゃったぞ。
Lee insisted that we come
and visit, so here we are!
さっさと開けろ！
Now open up!
（シノ）出かけているな…
なぜなら　出てこないからだ。
Maybe he went out.
Because he's not answering the door.
（ネジ）しかたがない　帰るか。
Too bad. Let's go then.
（キバ）匂いで　いるってのは
わかってんだけどな。
I can tell from his scent
that he's inside.
（シカマル）まだ　すねてんな
さっきのことで。
He's probably still upset
from earlier.
まったく
何だというのだね　キミたちは！
Damn it! What do you guys
want anyway?!
（シカマル）そうか
タイミングが悪かったな。
I see...
We came at a bad time.
じゃあ皆さん　帰ると…。
しかたない！
Well, let's go, guys—
Oh, all right! I'll hang out
with you guys!
つきあってやるってばよ。
（ネジ）何だと！？
What?!
またネジが　ドベだってばよ。
You lost again, Neji?
You're so bad at this.
僕　もうあがっちゃったもんね。
イカサマしてんじゃないだろうな。
I've been out too.
You'd better not be cheating.
やられました！
（キバ）負け犬の遠吠え！
I'm out!
The howl of a losing dog!
（シノ）そんなことはない
なぜなら…。
No such thing. The reason is...
（ネジ）やってられん　もう一度だ。
（シカマル）結局やんのかよ。
I can't stand this!
One more time!
So we're gonna keep playing?
もっと
ゆっくりしてきゃあいいのに。
You should stay longer.
悪いな。　遅くなると
母ちゃんが　うるせえからよ。
Sorry. Mom gets on my case
if I'm home late.
うちも　飯どきだけは…。
Me too. I can't miss dinner...
では　また。
おぅ。
– See you again.
– Yeah.
《今日が楽しかったからかな…。
Maybe 'cuz it was a fun day.
いつもよりなんか
部屋が広く感じんなぁ。
My room sorta feels roomier.
みんな
飯も食っていきゃよかったのに》
Everyone should've stuck
around to eat...
《こんな時に…》
Especially times like these.
時は満ちた。
The time is ripe...
うずまきナルト…
お前の心　覗かせてもらった。
Naruto Uzumaki...
I've seen what's inside your heart!
さぁ　限定月読を始めるぞ！
All right!
I'm starting the Limited Tsukuyomi!
I was tired of walking and didn't know what I should do
aruki tsukarete tohou ni kureta
my teacher told me to go towards a bright future
akarui mirai e sensei wa iu kedo
but which way should I go to find the light?
docchi ni aruitara hikari wa sasu kana
I have no idea at the moment so let's go
toriaezu wakaranai kedo ikouze
don't tell me things I want to hear
kirei goto nanka maji kan kanben desu
just give me something so powerful that it hurts
itai kurai tsuyoi yatsu wo choudai
I'm rebelling against the ordinary life
arikitari na mainichi ni hankou desu
burning up the mic with our rock
tagire m i c oretachi no rock
I can hear you are screaming
kimino koe ga kikoeru
that's the only thing that's real, let it explode
sore dake wa real sa hajikero
this song
kono uta
i can hear you are screaming
I'm running through the night on impulse
tsuki ugokasare shoudou no mama ni yoru wo kakenda
can't you see can't you see can't you see my face
I want to sense this moment not just the words, I want to sense you
kotoba ja nai ima dake wo kanjitetai kimi wo kanjitetai
i can hear you are screaming
keep on shouting and open the door to tomorrow
sakebi tsuzukete ashita no tobira wo kojihirakerunda
don't worry don't worry don't worry baby
I want to believe in us, not anyone else, I want to believe in my dream
dareka ja nai oretachi wo shinjitetai yume wo shinjitetai
Master Chen! What an honor
it is to see you again!
How could you have met someone
who died before you were born?
皆様　お変わりございませんか？
Master Chen was not dead!
美空ひばりです。
You're that brat from that day!
では最後まで
ごゆっくりお楽しみください。
I would never forget about you,
or about the Dragon's Eye!
『木曜８時のコンサート
名曲！　にっぽんの歌』。
Next time on Naruto Shippuden:
"The Old Master and the Dragon's Eye"
今回は　ご覧の豪華な歌手
１０組の皆さんによる→
So you're still a shinobi!